("DJ Got Us Fallin' In Love" by Usher)
♪ Usher ♪
♪ Yeah man ♪
♪ So we back in the club ♪
♪ With our bodies rockin'
from side to side ♪
♪ Side side to side ♪
♪ Thank God the week is done ♪
♪ I feel like a zombie gone back to life ♪
♪ Back back to life ♪
♪ Hands up and suddenly
we all got our hands up ♪
♪ No control of my body ♪
♪ Ain't I seen you before ♪
♪ I think I remember
those eyes eyes eyes ♪
♪ Eyes eyes eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin' in love again ♪
♪ Yeah baby tonight ♪
♪ So dance dance like it's the last ♪
♪ Last night of your life life ♪
♪ Gon' get you right ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin' in love again ♪
♪ Keep downing drinks like there's ♪
♪ No tomorrow there's just right ♪
♪ Now now now now now now now ♪
♪ Gonna set the roof on fire ♪
♪ Gonna burn this mother ♪
♪ Down down down down down down down ♪
♪ Hands up when the music drops ♪
♪ We both put our hands up ♪
♪ Put your hands on my body ♪
♪ Swear I seen you before ♪
♪ I think I remember those
eyes eyes eyes eyes ♪
♪ Eyes eyes eyes ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin' in love again ♪
♪ Yeah baby tonight ♪
♪ So dance dance like it's the last ♪
♪ Last night of your life life ♪
♪ Gon' get you right ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin' in love again ♪
♪ Usher don't lie ♪
♪ Hear no evil or speak
no evil or see no evil ♪
♪ Get it baby ♪
♪ Hope you catch that like T-O ♪
♪ That's how we roll my life
is a movie and you just TIVO ♪
♪ Mami got me twisted' like a dreadlock ♪
♪ She don't wrestle but
I got her in a headlock ♪
♪ Yabadabadoo make her bedrock
mami on fire red hots ♪
♪ Bada bing bada boom Mr.
Worldwide as I step in the room ♪
♪ I'm a hustler baby but that you knew ♪
♪ And tonight it's just me and you ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin' in love again ♪
♪ Yeah baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin in love ♪
♪ Fallin' in love again ♪
♪ So dance dance like it's the last ♪
♪ Last night of your life life ♪
♪ Gon' get you right ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us fallin' in love again ♪
♪ Yeah baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us falling in love again ♪
♪ So dance dance like
it's the last last night ♪
♪ Of your life life gon' get you right ♪
♪ 'Cause baby tonight ♪
♪ The DJ got us falling in love again ♪
♪ Yeah thank you DJ ♪